UNITE International Relations Department Publications 6000/027 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE International Relations Department Publications
1995-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/027 PUBS
5.5 cubic feet
5.5 linear ft.
Publications.
6796111
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R.Miles, June 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 12, 2015
Biographical / Historical
UNITE, the Union of Needle Trades, Industrial, and Textile Employees was formed in 1995 after a merger between the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
In 2004 they announced they would merge with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) which created UNITE HERE.
Jay Mazur served as president of UNITE from its beginning until his retirement in 2001. Bruce Raynor was elected president at that time and served until the HERE merger.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing trade--New York (State); Textile industry--New York (State); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. International Relations Dept.--Archives
6796111
- Africa (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Maputo Declaration on the Textiles, Clothing and Leather Industries, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Notes: Worker representatives from Mozambique, Zimbabwe, South Africa, Mauritius, Zambia, Swaziland, Lesotho, Tanzania, and Malawi.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: The Shopsteward, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: December, 1995.
  - Item 3: Shared Interest: In Focus, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (2001:Spring)
- Austria, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Hallo!, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.3/4 (2001:March/April)
    Language: German.
- Bangladesh, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Handbook on Trade Unions for Members of the Bangladesh Independent Garment-Workers Union (BIGU), 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: September, 1995.
- Africa: Sactwu News Izindaba, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: SACTWU News, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.7:no.16-17 (1995:Dec. 11) - v.8:no.1 (1996:Feb. 9)
  - Item 2: SACTWU News Izindaba, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1996:March 8) - v.12:no.4 (2000:Sept./Oct.)
- China, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report on ICFTU/ICFTU-APRO International Conference on Hong Kong Accord for a Better Tomorrow., 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: April 27-29, 1996
  - Item 2: The UN Official Report: Women Workers in China., 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Behind the Boom: Working Conditions in the Textile, Garment and Toy Industries in China., 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Behind the Label: Made in China, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: March, 1998.
  - Item 5: Union Action, 2001; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: May, 2001.
  - Item 6: The Flip-Side of Success: The Situation of Workers and Organizing in Foreign-Invested Electronics Enterprises in Guangdong, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: February 20, 1996.
- China Rights Forum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: China Rights Forum, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Fall 1995 and Winter 1995.
    Language: English; Chinese.
- China Labor Notes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: China Labor Notes, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.6:no.6/7 (1995:June/July) - v.7:no.3 (1996:March/April)
- China: Turning Point, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Turning Point, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- China Focus, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: China Focus, 1996; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.4:no.4 (1996:April 1) - v.4:no.5 (1996:May 1)
- China Labour Bulletin, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: China Labour Bulletin, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.16/17 (1995:Sept.) - no.45 (1998:Nov.Dec.). Missing issues no.32, 33, 38, and 39
- China Labour Bulletin, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: China Labour Bulletin, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.47 (1999:Mar./Apr.) - no.57 (2000:Nov./Dec.). Missing issues no.54 and 56.
- Europe, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The European Union: A Guide for Americans, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Hugo Paemen
  - Item 2: Trabajadores a Domicilio en Europa, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: Boletin no 1 (1996/1997)
  - Item 3: Made in Eastern Europe, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining in Western Europe, 1995-1996: Summary Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Giuseppe Fajertag
    Notes: July, 1996.
- France, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: CFDT Magazine, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.222 (1997:Jan.)
    Language: French.
- Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: One for All, All for One: German System of Social Security, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Die Neue Gewerkshaftszeitschrift Magazin, 1997; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: (1997:Feb.)
- Textil Bekleidung (Germany), Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Textil Bekleidung, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- India, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Gandhian Path in Trade Unionism, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Author: Navinchandra M. Barot
- Israel, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Jerusalem: Past, Present and Future, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Author: Bernard Wasserstein
    Notes: Policy Paper no.3 (1995:Oct.)
- Italy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: I Calabresi nel Mondo, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: Anno 1:no.8 (2000:Otobre)
    Language: Italian.
  - Item 2: Le Risposte-Chiave: Cos'e Previmoda?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Il Tuo Futuro e con noi, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: Flyer.
  - Item 4: Il Tuo Futuro e con noi, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: Booklet.
- Il Lavoro (Italy), Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Il Lavoro, 2001; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: Anno 73:n.2 (2001:gennaio 19) - Anno 73:n.7 (2001:febbraio 23). Missing Anno 73:n.4.
- Japan Labor Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Japan Labor Bulletin, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.34:no.7 (1995:July) - v.35:no.1o (1996:OCt.), v.39:no.9 (2000:Sept.). Missing v.35:no.2.
- Japanese Working Life Profile, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Japanese Working Life Profile, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: Labor statistics. 1993-1994; 1996-1997; 1997- 1998.
    Language: English;Japanese.
- Japan Institute of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: What is JIL?, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Japan as Seen by the Foreign Labour-related Leaders., 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Labour-Management Relations in Japan, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Japanese Economy and Labor Series, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Shunto Wage Offensive, 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Author: Akira Takanashi
    Notes: Japanese Economy and Labor Series, no.1. Two copies.
  - Item 2: Employment Insurance Law, 1997; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: Japanese Economy and Labor Series, no.3.
- Japan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Spring Struggle for a Better Living, 1996: Challenge to Change, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: RENGO White Paper
  - Item 2: WWN, 2000; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (2000:June 12)
  - Item 3: Creating a Dynamic Economy Through Structural Reform, 1996; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Committee for the Study of Labor Issues
    Notes: NIKKEIREN Position Paper.
- Korea, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Korea's Economy, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: v.13 (1997); v.15 (1999)
- Latin and Central America, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: CNTD, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.19:no.99 (1997:Aug.)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: Que Estan Haciendo en Argentina, en America, y el Mundo?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Informa el Centro de Solidaridad, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Nocoes de Economia: Reajuste e Politica Salarial, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Marco Antonio Jorge
    Notes: Caderno 1.
    Language: Portuguese.
  - Item 5: Revista do Sindicato, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.5 (1995:Setembro)
  - Item 6: The U.S. in Haiti: How to Get Rich on 11 an Hour, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: National Labor Committee Education Fund
    Notes: A Report for the National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights in Central America.
  - Item 7: Behind Closed Doors: The Workers Who Make Our Clothes, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: University Students Investigate Factories in Central America
  - Item 8: Better Neighbors: A Blueprint for Just U.S. Relations whti Latin America and the Caribbean., 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Lisa Haugaard
  - Item 9: De la Crisis al Desarrollo, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Jornal da Forca, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.12 (1999:Marco)
- Latin and Central America: Informa El IADSL, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Informa el I.A.D.S.L., 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: Boletin 6, 8-12 (1996), Boletin 3-4 (1997).
- Latin and Central America: Contacto, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Contacto, 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30:no.65 (1995:Oct.), v.31:no.69 (1996:Sept.), v.36:no.87 (2001:Mar./Apr.)
- Latin and Central America: Quehaceres, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Que Haceres, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: January and March
- Mexico, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Gaceta Informativa: Plataforma 2000, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.11:no.145 (2000:Dec.)
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO Mexican Trip, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: January 22-23, 1998. Mexico City
  - Item 3: "Apparel City" The Investors Handbook., Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: Ciudad de la Confeccion
  - Item 4: Parque Industrial: Cuidad de la Confeccion, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: Reclutamiento
- FNV News (Netherlands), Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: FNV News, 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.14 (1995:Dec.) - no.21 (1999:Dec.). Missing no.17.
- Norway, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Magasinet for Fagorganiserte, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: nr.9 (2000:Nov.)
    Language: Norwegian.
- United Kingdom, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A Review of UK Company Codes of Conduct., 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Clare Ferguson
    Notes: Social Development Division Report
- KFAT (United Kingdom), Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: KFAT News, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.15 (1995:Summer) - no.27 (1998:Summer). Missing issues no.20-25.
- T&G Record (United Kingdom), Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: T&G Reocrd, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Child Labor Booklets [Folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Action Against Child Labour: The Turk-Is Model, 1998; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Ozcan Karabulut
    Notes: Turk-Is Publication no.225
  - Item 2: Children Are Our Future: Child Labour is Our Future Denied, End Child Labour NOW!, 2000; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: No Time To Play: Child Workers in the Global Economy, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Eileen Cadman
    Notes: Trade Union Campaign for a Social Cause.
  - Item 4: The Small Hands of Slavery: Bonded Child Labor in India, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Trade Unions and Child Labour, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Notes: labour Education no.102. Two copies.
- Child Labor Booklets [Folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Youth and the Trade Unions: Common Interest, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Police Abuse and Killings of Street Children in India, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Child Labor: Issues and Directions for the World Bank, 1998; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Peter Fallon; Zafiris Tzannatos
    Notes: Social Protection Human Development Network
  - Item 4: Child Labor in Islamabad, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Sarah Javed; Zarina Jillani
  - Item 5: Child Labour: Targeting the Intolerable, 1998; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Notes: Internatinal Labour Conference, 86th Session, Report VI (1).
- Child Labor Pamphlets [Folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: International Programme on the Elimination of Child Labour (IPEC), Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The BIGU/AAFLI Joint Program for Former Child Garment Workers: The Sweatshop Alternative, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: Three copies
  - Item 3: Odhikar: A Coalition for Human Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Introducing Lawyers for Human Rights and Legal Aid, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Beyond Borders of Child Labour in the Garment Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: Child Labour Project. Three copies
  - Item 6: Child Labor: The Conspiracy of Silence, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: A Brief Introduction of Surjamukhi Shisu Sangha, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Save the Children, Preserve the Environment: NASPEC at a Glance., 1997; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Child and Adult Labour in the Garment Export Industry of Tirupur, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: The International Child Labor Elimination Act, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Know Your Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Child Labor Pamphlets [Folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Trafficking of Women and Children in Pakistan: The Flesh Trade Report, 1995-1996, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: 1998 Child Labor Stamp: Commemorating Child Labor Reform, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Thursday's Child, 1997; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Children Without Childhoods, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Eliminating Child Labour, 1995; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Free The Children Report, 1997; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: HomeWorkers News Bulletin, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: Special Issue 1996: Child Labour in Bangladesh.
    Language: English;Bengali.
  - Item 8: Lifting the Veil at Alfred Angelo, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Sweatshops: on the March to End Sweatshop Labor, 1999; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: Co-op America Quarterly, no.49 (1999:Fall)
  - Item 10: Report of the Seminar for International Trade Secretariats on Developing National and International Trade Union Strategies to Combat Child Labour, 1997; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Bureau for Workers' Activities (ACTRAV)
    Notes: April 7-8, 1997
  - Item 11: Footprings, 1999; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1999:May)
  - Item 12: Children as Work: A Handbook on Child Labour for Public Service Workers, 1999; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Child Labor Monitor, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Child Labor Monitor, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1995:Dec.) - v.10:no.3 (2000:Winter). Missing several issues.
- Child Labor: Rugmark, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: RUGMARK Consumer Campaign: Organizers Kit, 1995; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: RUGMARK After One Year: Appraisal of a New Effort at Social Marketing in the Interest of Children, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: RUGMARK Bulletin 2000, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
- The Apparel Industry and Codes of Conduct, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Apparel Industry and Codes of Conduct: A Solution to the International Child Labor Problem?, 1996; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Author: Bureau of International Labor Affairs
- The Apparel Industry and Codes of Conduct copy 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Apparel Industry and Codes of Conduct: A Solution to the International Child Labor Problem?, 1996; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 2
- Child Labor: By the Sweat and Toil of Children Vol. II, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: By the Sweat & Toil of Children, 1995; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 2: The Use of Chld Labor in U.S. Agricultural Imports and Forced and Bonded Child Labor
- Child Labor: By the Sweat and the Toil of Children Vol. IV, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: By the Sweat & Toil of Children, 1997; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 4: Comsumer Labels and Child labor
- Child Labor: By the Sweat and Toil of Children Vol. V copy 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: By the Sweat & Toil of Children, 1998; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 5: Efforts to Eliminate Child Labor
- Child Labor: By the Sweat and Toil of Children Vol. V copy 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: By the Sweat & Toil of Children, 1998; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 5: Efforts to Eliminate Child Labor. Copy 2.
- Child Labor: SPARC, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: SPARC, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.6, 11-13
- Global Labor Standards and the Apparel Industry, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Global Labor Standards and the Apparel Industry: Can We Regulate Global Production?, 1998; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Ethics, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Principles for Global Corporate Responsibility: Bench Marks for Measuring Business Performance., 1995; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Notes: The Corporate Examiner, v.24:no.2/4 (1995:Sept. 1)
  - Item 2: Business Ethics in the Textile, Clothing and Footwear (TCF) Industries: Codes of Ethics., 1997; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Jean-Paul Sajhau
    Notes: Sectoral Activities Programme Working Papers
  - Item 3: Purpose; Principles; Programme; Membership Information, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Globalization/Multinationals, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 1996 Annual Report, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: 1996 Annual Report, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Notes: Newsletter, v.8:no.1 (1998:Spring)
  - Item 3: 1996 Annual Report, 1999; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Notes: Newsletter, v.9:no.1 (1999:Spring)
  - Item 4: The Global Economy, 1997; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Notes: Current History, v.96:no.613 (1997:Nov.)
  - Item 5: Global Pay Survey, 1999; Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Author: Frances Cairncross
    Notes: The Economist, May 8-9, 1999
- Homework, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Home Work, 1996; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Notes: Internatinal Labour Conference, 83th Session, Report IV (2B).
- HomeNet (Homework), Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: HomeNet, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- NAFTA, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Challenging "Free Trade" in the Americas: Building Common Responses. Country Report: Canada, 1996; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 6-7, 1996. Two copies
  - Item 2: Challenging "Free Trade" in the Americas: Building Common Responses. Country Report: Mexico, 1996; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 6-7, 1996.
  - Item 3: NAFTA at Two Years: The Human and Environmental Toll, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Author: Sarah Anderson; John Cavanagh; Ajantha Subramanian
  - Item 4: NAFTA Expansion: Off the Fast Track, On the Right Track, 1997; Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Author: Public Policy Department
  - Item 5: UNITE FIGHTsize: The NAFTA Scam, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: UNITE Temas de Lucha: El Embuste del Libre Comercio, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Women Pamphlets, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Breaking the Legacy of Invisibility, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Claiming Our Rights! Women and Trade Unions, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Trade Union Vision Document: Changing the World Through Equality, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Asian and Pacific Regional Organisation
  - Item 4: Worlds Apart: Women and the Global Economy, 1996; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Natacha David
  - Item 5: Asia's Working Women Demand a Share of the Economic Miracle, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Remarks by First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton: United Nations Fourth World Conference on Women, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Hillary Rodham Clinton
    Notes: September 5-6, 1995.
  - Item 7: Facts on Working Women, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Women's Bureau
    Notes: no.98-1 (1998:May)
  - Item 8: Facts on Working Women, 1997; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The UN Official Report: Women Workers in China., 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: PSI Women, 2001; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.9 (2001:Feb.)
  - Item 11: Working Women Count: Honor Roll Update, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: October, 1995.
  - Item 12: Regional Conference on Trafficking in Women and Children in South Asia, 1997; Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Harassment of Women at the Workplace: Summary Report, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: Nazish Brohi
    Notes: A Document of the Working Women's Support Center (WWSC)
- Asian Women Workers Newsletter, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Asian Women Workers Newsletter, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.14:no.3-4; v.15:no.1-2, 4; v.16:no.2-3; v.20:no.1
- Companeras, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Companeras, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.22-23.
- FLWWomen, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: FLWWomen, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.1 (1996:Mar.); no.2 (1996:June); no.1 (1997:Mar.)
- Worker's/Human Rights, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: China: The Cost of Putting Business First, 1996; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (C) (1996:July)
  - Item 2: Mexico: Labor Rights and NAFTA, a Case Study, 1996; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (B) (1996:Sept.)
  - Item 3: Burma/Thailand: Unwanted and Unprotected: Burmese Refugees in Thailand, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.10:no.6 (C) (1998:Oct.)
  - Item 4: The Most Repressive Regimes of 1999, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Author: Commission on Human Rights
    Notes: A Special Report to the 55th Session of the United Nations Commission on Human Rights in Geneva
  - Item 5: The Universal Declaration of Human Rights, 1948-1998, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: In Your Hands: Community Action Guide for Human Rights Year and Beyond, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)